https://www.cornerstonebank.com/about-us/privacy-policy/

New Alert: Our branch lobbies are currently closed. Drive-ups will continue to operate on their normal schedules. Our Southbridge Main Office will continue to be open to customers. Skip to primary navigation Skip to content Skip to primary sidebarLocations
Contact Us
Customer Service
Bank Holidays
About Us
Bank History
2018 Annual Report
Officers
Directors and Corporators
Search
Home About Us Privacy PolicyThe following statement discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. The information we receive depends upon your actions when visiting this website.
When you visit our website, we collect the following information:
The (IP) address, which we use for the purpose of counting the volume of requests we receive; and
Information that you knowingly and voluntarily provide when you fill in your name, address, and any other information on the Contact form, other forms, or when you e-mail us.
When you voluntarily choose to send us information by accessing our website, you consent to our use of the information as stated in this notice. The information you voluntarily supply to us is used by us first and foremost to process your request or inquiry. The information may also be used by us to develop, refine, and provide products, services, and opportunities that help us meet the financial needs of our customers.
FACTS
WHAT DOES CORNERSTONE BANK DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number
Income
Account balances
Payment history
Credit history
Assets
When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How?
All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons Cornerstone Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does Cornerstone Bank share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes– such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes – to offer our products and services to you
Yes
No
For joint marketing with other financial companies
Yes
No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your transactions and experiences
No
We Don’t Share
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness
No
We Don’t Share
For our affiliates to market to you
No
We Don’t Share
For nonaffiliates to market to you
No
We Don’t Share
Questions?
Call toll-free 800-939-9103
Who We Are
Who is providing this notice?
Cornerstone Bank
What We Do
How does Cornerstone Bank protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
We restrict access to your personal information to only those employees who need to know. We require confidentiality agreements with third party vendors needed for products and services.
How does Cornerstone Bank collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
Open an account
Deposit money
Pay your bills
Apply for a loan
Make a wire transfer
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. (See below for more on your rights under state law.)
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
Cornerstone Bank has no affiliates.
Nonaffiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
Cornerstone Bank does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
Joint Marketing
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
Our joint marketing partners can include companies such as insurance providers.
Other Important Information
We adhere to Massachusetts Data Protection Law; Standards For The Protection Of Personal Information Of Residents Of The Commonwealth, that mandates personal information be encrypted when stored on portable devices, or transmitted wirelessly or on public networks. Additionally, the regulation calls on businesses to utilize up-to-date firewall protection that creates an electronic gatekeeper between data and the outside world and only permits authorized users to access or transmit data according to preset rules.
Children’s Online Privacy, The law requires parental consent to collect or use information from a child under 13. If you are a child under 13, please show this to your parents and do not use the online services of this institution without verifiable parental consent pursuant to the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act.
Primary SidebarAbout Us2020 Scholarship Recipients
Bank History
Career Opportunities
Charitable Donations
Charitable Donation Policy
Charitable Donation Requests
Contact Us
Ask Us A Question
What is Identity Theft?
Categories
Company News (67)
Featured (8)
